{
    "id": "14182de7ba364ba398fb099bff9a3793",
    "title": "Active And Passive Voice Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Most things ………………….. plastic these days.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "made of",
                "are made of"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "3be9a640b86144f0a1d8cd5bab298121"
        },
        {
            "question": "My mother ……………….. wine from strawberries.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "makes",
                "is made"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "332e0b29e72c451f8731056340cfdc90"
        },
        {
            "question": "The house …………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is built",
                "is being built"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "11ef35719c024793877cdd35da5fcf23"
        },
        {
            "question": "This bag …………………. of leather.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "made",
                "is made"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "81ff8d81ae6a479693a261030ff61842"
        },
        {
            "question": "It ………………. disappeared. I can’t see it now.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "has",
                "has been"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "90a58dd46b6449399e9bf22f6413a705"
        },
        {
            "question": "Their house ………………… last week.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "sold",
                "was sold"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "6038de8ec9404d2d8c4d2f68d5ad57ab"
        },
        {
            "question": "Do you think that the work ………………… by Friday?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is completed",
                "will be completed"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a6ca7fe09d7f44618764959249be10fc"
        },
        {
            "question": "These tablets ………………. with food.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "need to take",
                "need to be taken"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "152452f530a148058b76ca797a729290"
        },
        {
            "question": "The postman …………………. this letter in the morning.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "delivered",
                "was delivered"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "200637e1176c41f6aee8410a17658d50"
        },
        {
            "question": "You ………………. the money last week.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "should sent",
                "should have sent"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "255f59fe4635485c943d729a85bf70f7"
        }
    ]
}